

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

# PERSONAL DETAILS

D.O.B

22 st April 1981

Contact:

Tel: +48 (733) 013 108

<u>Email:</u> rafalxpl@gmail.com

Place of birth: Białystok, Polanc

Nationality: Polish

# PORTFOLIO

visual3design.com

# INTERESTS:

Gaming, Illustration, Photography, Automotive

# PROFILE



**Bē** Behance: behance.net/rafalxpl

Deviantart rafalxpl.deviantart.com

#### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I'm a Design Director with 17 years of graphic design and leadership experience in the branding, marketing, advertising and webdesign.

My professional interests include involvement in the design community and design collaboration. I have more than 5 years experience working as a responsive web designer.

I am currently available for freelance or full time work.

# EDUCATION

<b>2006-2007</b> Chicago, USA	0	EAST-WEST UNIVERSITY CHICAGO ESL course
<b>2003-2006</b> Łódź, Poland	Ò	STUDY OF COMPUTER GRAPHICS IN LODZ 3D Animation - Web Design
2001-2003 Białystok Poland	O	SCHOOL OF INFORMATICS Windows Server Administrator, Web Design
<b>1996-2001</b> Suprasl, Poland	Ö	HIGH SCHOOL OF ART ACADEMY Visual arts, especially illustration, painting, photography, sculpture, and graphic design

# EXPERIENCE

2013-2017 Schaumburg	0	WEBTOMED, L.L.C.  Web Designer - Responsive Medical Website Designer, Identity, UX UI Design
<b>2012 - 2013</b> Chicago	0	KREATE Freelancer / Web Designer , Identity, UX UI Design
<b>2011 - 2012</b> Chicago	0	DMC, INC. Freelancer / Web Designer , Identity, UX UI Design
2008 - 2011 Chicago	O	VISUAL3DESIGN Graphic Designer / Web Designer , Identity, UX UI Design
2007 - 2008 Chicago	0	MAGAZYN "PLUS" Graphic Designer
2006 - 2007 Chicago	Ö	BLUEBOX Graphic Designer

# SKILLSET

Web Design	Design Software	Other
Responsive Web Design	Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Corel,	Print Design: Color
An understanding of UI/ UX design		Space, Printing Processes, Color Separation, Color Theory
Basic HTML & CSS	Video Editing	Typography
Grid Layout Wireframes	Premiere / After Effects	Project management experience
Design Subscription	3D know-how and experience - 3Ds Max, Cinema 4d, ZBrush,	CMS knowledge
E-newsletter		Ability to work under pressure